streamfree.tv 2018-01-19

# Privacy Policy - Stream FREE TV

## **Privacy Policy for www.streamfree.tv**

If you require any more  information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to  contact us by email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

At www.streamfree.tv, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.streamfree.tv and how it is used.

**Amazon Affiliate Disclosure Statement**

StreamFREE.TV is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program,  
an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.streamfree.tv makes use of log files. The information  
inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of  
browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit  
pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s  
movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and  
other such information are not linked to any information that is personally  
identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.streamfree.tv does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record  
user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web  
page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the  
visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.::Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.streamfree.tv.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve  
ads to users based on their visit to www.streamfree.tv and other sites on the  
Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting  
the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL –  
http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners  
may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include  
….  
**Google Adsense**

These third-party ad servers or ad networks  
use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.streamfree.tv  
send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when  
this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons )  
may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of  
their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you  
see.

www.streamfree.tv has no access to or control over these cookies  
that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out  
of certain practices. www.streamfree.tv’s privacy policy does not apply to, and  
we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual  
browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific  
web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
